https://www.boggycreek.org/privacy-statement/

Introduction
Camp Boggy Creek is committed to maintaining your privacy and has created the following guidelines. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This information is provided as your guide regarding how we will handle information that we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.
1. Use of Links
Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers. Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you’d like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send an email to info@campboggycreek.org with the subject “Link request.”
2. Use of Text and Images
If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to info@campboggycreek.org. Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page. Information about using our logo and images is available in Media Resources.
3. Accessibility
This Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at info@campboggycreek.org
4. Reading or Downloading
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University’s domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.
We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
5. Security of Donor Privacy
Camp Boggy Creek strives to ensure that donor information is protected by adhering to applicable data compliance and security standards. Our systems utilize layered security and only selected employees have access to hard copies of your personal information. To review our Donor Privacy Policy please click here.
All online transactions are processed on a secure server and the information entered on our donate page is secured through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption prior to its transmission (this refers to the “https” on our donation page showing that information entered on that page is encrypted).
Blackbaud Payment Service (BBPS) stores credit card information. This is integrated with Payment Application Data Security Standard (PA-DSS) compliant versions of The Raiser’s Edge (which is our fundraising database) along with Blackbaud NetCommunity (our web hosting and content management system).  BBPS is a “cloud” program that enables it to adhere to The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS).
Credit card numbers and data are not visible in any of our software applications since card information is stored on BBPS.  Instead, in each software application, reference tokens replace credit card numbers.
For example, the software application connects to the BBPS when credit card transactions are processed such as with recurring gifts. Then the reference token in the software application summons the stored credit card number for use in the transaction. Staff are not able to access your credit card information at any time.
All of our credit card transactions are processed by Blackbaud Merchant & Payment Services and the donation is recorded on credit card statements as Camp Boggy Creek.
In regards to other privacy measures, our site uses cookies (small pieces of text a website directs to the visitors browser and that deliver a more targeted and customized experience for the visitor/user through recognition). For instance cookies track the type of browser a visitor used, his/her language settings,user password/ID, etc. Cookies enable signing up for our services easier for users and allow our website to remember user search preferences and to track how many visitors visit our website.
This information is not sold to any third-party or commercial entities. Occasionally we engage in partnerships with third-party vendors who utilize user cookies for the use of recognizing them.
If you have any questions regarding the security of your credit card donation online, any privacy concerns and/or would like to opt out of any third party usage of your information please e-mail us at info@campboggycreek.org or call 352-483-4200.
6. Online Profile Updates and Donations
If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the “Opt Out” section below.
7. Sending us an Email
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We will not share your name or email address with any outside parties.
8. Children and Privacy
For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When children send an email to us, their online contact information (email address) is not utilized for ongoing communication and is not maintained in retrievable form.
9. Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through our contact us page at: https://www.boggycreek.org/contact-us/. In addition, all mailings and electronic mailings have an opt-out option. You may request that any communications from Camp Boggy Creek be stopped at any time by notifying us at info@campboggycreek.org. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us by contacting us. If you provide us with personal information it will remain in our database, but you can always opt-out of unwanted communications.
10. Questions about our policies
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at: info@campboggycreek.org.
Terms and Conditions:
Camp Boggy Creek world wide website is provided to you free of charge, “as is.”
You may only use Camp Boggy Creek world wide website for legal purposes. You may not use Camp Boggy Creek world wide website to collect or harvest personal information, including internet addresses, about Camp Boggy Creek world wide website users.
Camp Boggy Creek uses its best efforts to maintain Camp Boggy Creek world wide website but is not responsible for the results of any defects that exist in Camp Boggy Creek world wide website, or any resulting lost profits or other consequential damages. You should not assume that Camp Boggy Creek world wide website or its content is error-free or that it will be suitable for the particular purpose that you have in mind when using it.
Camp Boggy Creek may, in its sole discretion and at any time, modify or discontinue Camp Boggy Creek world wide website; limit, terminate or suspend your use of or access to Camp Boggy Creek world wide website; and/or make changes to these Terms of Use.
Copyright Notice:
The documents and information on this Web site are copyrighted materials of Camp Boggy Creek. Reproduction or storage of materials retrieved from this service is subject to the U.S. Copyright Act of 1976, Title 17 U.S.C.
Camp Boggy Creek and Camp Boggy Creek logo are registered trademarks of Camp Boggy Creek. All rights reserved. Camp Boggy Creek.
"I remember when I was going through chemo and I came here. I felt like a normal kid. I could take my bandana off and not worry about people staring at me."
- Timothy, Camper
The CampAbout Us
Camp Tour
Camp Stories
Our Leadership
Media / Publications
Employment
Location
©2020 Camp Boggy Creek All Rights Reserved.
X
Search
